[{"answer": "You stink. You know you stink. What is this", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Beard.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Oh. Your ballet tickets", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Yeah, yeah, maybe I can get him to draw a picture of her for you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Beard.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Yeah, yeah. I think he will", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Thank you. You're a good man. Bless you", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Beard.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Where am I going?  At the police station", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Woah, woah, that's mine", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Beard.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "No, no, I didn't say you could keep it. You see I don't give away tupperware", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Because when you join that team it's not a whim. He likes his team. He's set with that team", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Beard.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Yeah, we do. We do have a good team", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "They're only comfortable with", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Beard.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Of course you did. Everyone gets along great when there's no possibility of sex", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I realize that", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Beard.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Yes I am. At my friend's apartment. He is on the phone", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "What about a plastic bag", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Beard.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "What is the difference", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Yeah well we go way back", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Beard.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Who's to say it didn't", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "So did you describe yourself to her over the phone", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Beard.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What did you say to her", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Yes I did", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Beard.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "What do you think I said", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What did you say to her", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Beard.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I told her the truth", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Beard.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Yes, as I see it", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "You only think that because you know me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Beard.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I noticed people staring at my head because they like what they see", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Beard.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "No. I'm sick of shaking. You've got to shake everything. my friend picks up the bottle and shakes it gently", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Yeah, that's a real nuisance. This is killing me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Beard.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "So tonight are you going to make the move", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "That's an interesting question", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Beard.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "How so? I'll tell you how so. She's bald", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "How so? I'll tell you how so. She's bald", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Beard.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "What do you think I mean bald? Bald. Bald bald", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "What do you think I mean bald? Bald. Bald bald", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Beard.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "She's bald", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "Oh, uh, wait a second. Would you like to come, upstairs", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Beard.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "Yeah. Upstairs", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "She's as good as anybody else", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Beard.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Yeah you've had like a religious awakening. You're like a bal", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Did my friend's finance kidnap that place and take her to that place? And if so, did she enjoy it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Beard.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Did my friend sleep with my friend again", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Yeah, I guess I never really stood a chance", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Beard.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Yeah.  Thanks. Is Melrose Place on", "qsentId": 46}]